broadcast tonight taking flight of big storm gives way to a spectacular show millions make it home in time to celebrate tonight how Americans are giving thanks across the country and serving far from home
今晚播出服用大风暴的飞行让位给大戏百万使其在回家的时间来庆祝今晚怎么美国人是给全国各地的感谢，并从家里远远服务
making a map from turkey dinner to stores open earlier than ever had some people acting tonight Thanksgiving
从制作火鸡大餐的地图专卖店早于过一些人今晚行动感恩开启
children this one holiday weekend Obamacare advocates make a push to get young people to sign up
孩子这一个周末假期Obamacare的倡导者拨打按键让年轻人报名
Best in Show in annual Thanksgiving family tradition of crown jewel takes the wind
最佳展示在皇冠上的明珠的一年一度的感恩家风需要风
NBC News New York NBC Nightly News with Brian Williams
NBC新闻纽约NBC晚间新闻与布赖恩·威廉斯
leaving and happy Thanksgiving on Kate snow in for Brian tonight and let start with something to be thankful for despite some diet predictions and worries that a winter storm might have a major impact on holiday festivities in travel
在凯特雪留下快乐的感恩节为布赖恩今晚，让开始的东西要感谢的，尽管一些减肥的预测和担心冬季风暴可能对旅游节日庆祝活动产生重大影响
flight delays has subsided and while there was snow and rain millions of Americans were able to celebrate the holiday today with family
航班延误已经消退，虽然有雨雪百万计的美国人能够在今天庆祝节日与家人
hi Windsor New York called by this morning to allow the Macy's Thanksgiving Day Parade to go ahead is Plan B si skater starts off tonight
喜温莎纽约调用今早让梅西感恩节大游行继续前进的B计划SI选手今晚开始起飞
from the parade route in Katy
从凯蒂的巡游路线
hey there to American greeting 736 million pounds of turkey the day before old was good chicken sixth Avenue right here with a buzz with people crowd lining the streets for Thanksgiving Day Parade that went off without a hitch
哎还有美国前问候老的一天7.36亿磅火鸡是好的鸡第六大道就在这里与人排队围观的感恩节游行的还算顺利街头时髦
million people line Street in Bremen cold not knowing if the stars of the 87th annual Macy's Thanksgiving Day Parade what show up
万人行街不来梅冷不知道如果87年梅西感恩节大游行的明星有什么显示
right now
现在
perfect Parade was Spider Man
完美的游行是蜘蛛侠
left arm punctured and Clayton
左手臂刺破和克莱顿
snag a tree round corner Thanksgiving traditions continued always cross the country even after a wet and wavy sew in
捡个树圆角感恩节的传统，即使在湿的和波浪形缝在继续总是越过国家
ways and cancelled flights today
方式和取消的航班今天
weather headaches didn't damp in the holiday spirit in Washington the first family had a traditional dinner at the White House today including turkey ham in 9 times of Pi
天气头痛并没有在节日的精神在华盛顿的第一个家庭今天有一个传统的晚宴在白宫，包括火鸡火腿皮的9倍受潮
before sitting down to eat the president called troops to wish someone happy holidays and thank them keep razors today in a web address
坐下来吃饭的总裁之前调用军队希望有人节日快乐，并感谢他们今天保持剃须刀的网址
matter what are differences raw part of one American family
不管是什么区别之一美国家庭的一部分原料
Atlanta Volunteers of hot meals free clothing and more than 6 ounces in need
的热饭免费服装亚特兰大志愿者和超过6盎司的需要
2000 and in Santa Barbara people showed up to help in care packages the victims of typhoon hayain in the Philippines
2000年和圣巴巴拉人出现在护理包帮助台风hayain的受害者在菲律宾
today also mark the first day of Hanukkah the two holidays haven't fallen on the same day 1888 and in Arabic 1 New York 9 year old Pinus decided to invent a turkey shaped menorah call the monarchy
今天也标志着光明节第一天的两个节日都没有落在1888的同一天和阿拉伯语1纽约9岁的松决定发明一个火鸡形灯台致电君主制
all day crown wine from Snowy Detroit
从雪域底特律所有天冠酒
Grawn mi
Grawn英里
thanksgivukkah Thanksgiving and Hanukkah probably won't fall on the same day confirmed maybe 70000 years or so if you have dreams about Creek turkey cranberry stuffing sandwich bread is actually latkes better make that dream a reality now
thanksgivukkah感恩节和光明节可能不会落在同一天，也许证实了7万年左右，如果你有梦想大约溪火鸡蔓越莓馅夹心面包其实是latkes更好地使现在的梦想成为现实
k teacher on the streets of New York tonight lots of Turkey being served up for our troops overseas tonight to tens of thousands are serving another Thanksgiving in Afghanistan
ķ老师在纽约今晚很多土耳其今晚被送达我们的海外派兵到几万所服务的另一个感恩节在阿富汗街头
far from home far from their families for most of them it will likely be the last Thanksgiving there before coming home as the US prepare to withdraw most troops by next summer
远离家乡，远离亲人，他们大多也将可能是最后一个感恩节有回家之前，为美国准备在明年夏天撤离大部分军队
Archie foreign correspondent Richard Engel is in Afghanistan tonight
阿奇外国记者理查德·恩格尔是在阿富汗今晚
29.wav
grieving Kate there are still about 45 thousand US troops are in Afghanistan today just feeding them with a military operation in itself 73
悲痛的凯特仍有约45000美军在阿富汗今天刚喂他们本身的军事行动73
house in pounds of turkey 55 thousand pounds of beef 20000 pies but for the soldiers on outpost like this one was welcome break
房子磅的火鸡55000磅牛肉20000馅饼的，但用于前哨像这样的士兵是值得欢迎的突破
set fire based welcome won the last American outpost in the mountains in the eastern Afghanistan Happy Thanksgiving Thanksgiving started with a turkey trot
一套基于火灾欢迎赢得了最后的美国前哨在山中的阿富汗东部感恩节快乐感恩节开始与土耳其小跑
5:45 a.m.
上午05时45分
3.2 steep miles they call it the climb to glory
3.2陡英里，他们把它叫做攀登到荣耀
Parker still counting 80 pounds of motor
帕克仍然计数80磅电机
winter was Brian Campbell that's him in blue 24 from Maple Grove Minnesota
冬季是布赖恩·坎贝尔就是他在蓝从24 Maple Grove的明尼苏达州
even better than climb to glory bragging rights for cancel a promotion to p**** to knit
对于取消晋升为p ****编织甚至比攀登到荣耀更好地吹牛的权利
chaos company 10th Mountain Division down today
混乱的公司第10山地师今日下跌
gymtyme poker volleyball at noon sharp child turkey and ham stuffing inside
gymtyme扑克排球中午锋利孩子火鸡和火腿里面馅
internal military tradition commander rank
内部的军事传统指挥官军衔
what to do excerpt from a summer place
怎样从一个夏天的地方做摘录
we caught up with lieutenant Campbell again and found out reach shape
我们赶上了坎贝尔中尉再次发现够不着形状
he's been training for wedding reception
他已经训练了婚礼招待会
I got a wedding coming out when I get back home so get ready for that a honeymoon body
我得到了一个婚礼出来，当我回家所以准备为一个蜜月体
Campbell married Kelsey last year propose on Thanksgiving diploid 2 months later play never had a party last night together
坎贝尔结婚凯尔西去年提出在感恩二倍体以后2个月玩从未有过的党昨晚在一起
Arizona
亚利桑那
what is popcorn
什么是爆米花
Kelsey's starting a new job as a nurse the late shift so she's not having a Thanksgiving this year just a phone call
Kelsey的开始一个新的工作，作为一个护士晚班，所以她不是今年有一个感恩节只需一个电话
I feel like you're breaking tradition anything like Thanksgiving
我觉得像你打破传统，什么样的感恩节
the truth today got a taste of home zone for a little while did much feel like one
今天回到家区的味道了一小会儿的真相远没有感觉像1
MK for the soldiers here when the Sun comes up in a few hours no post holiday shopping no leftover turkey sandwiches its back to the mission back to the war tapes
MK在这里的战士，当太阳升起几个小时后无假日购物没有剩的火鸡三明治其回使命回到了战争的磁带
Richard Engel in Afghanistan with their service even before live turkeys were in the oven in hours before football games holiday shopping kicked off of
理查德·恩格尔在阿富汗与他们的服务，甚至在现场火鸡在烤箱以小时前橄榄球比赛的假日购物拉开序幕
the country this morning and it creeps burlier an earlier more than a dozen major retailers from Target to Macys are open
该国今天上午和它爬行burlier更早十几主要的零售商从目标到梅西是开放的
National Retail Federation survey 33 million people are expected to shop today and I have some people asking if it's all too much too soon NBC John yang
全国零售联合会调查3300万人，预计今日到店，我有一些人问，如果这一切都太多太快NBC约翰阳
before dawn in suburban Chicago does a ratio is what you want to be first in line at Kmart husband Bobby's mom Warrior here to
黎明在芝加哥郊区之前没有一个比你想成为什么第一线在凯马特丈夫鲍比的妈妈战士在这里
whatever the boss says today go get the camera
不管老板说今天去拿相机
Barbie Power Wheels
芭比动力轮
what part of the Trail of a Nintendo video game for son only know your in stock right now I just say
什么任天堂视频游戏的儿子足迹的部分只知道你的股票，现在我只想说
$100
百美元
wheezing from store to store the family tradition what you like a lot better on Black Friday
从商店喘息你喜欢什么好了很多存储家族传统的黑色周五
send out at home with my 24 and 11 else that goes I'm a little bit longer this is all for them
送出去在家中与我的24和11个其他事物去我久一点这一切都是为了他们
Thanksgiving dinner Shearwater daughter outside Walmart analytics holiday Silvis you'll be up about 4 percent from where
沃尔玛分析假期旅游Silvis以外的感恩节晚餐海鸥的女儿你会从其中约4％
online the top destination for the first time by opening to grab their share but it may not work
在线打开来抓住他们的份额，但它可能无法正常工作的首选目的地，第一次
you don't have more relativism are people on your holiday list just because there more hours or even more days to the sale period
你没有更多的相对人是你的假期表上，只是因为有更多的时间，甚至更多天的销售期
some stores are joining including Nordstrom Costco in Marshalls 1 New York area electronics chain is boasting about it
一些商店也加入其中包括诺思通在Costco公司1执法官纽约地区的电子产品连锁店的吹嘘它
PC Richard and son Thanksgiving should be spent at home
PC Richard和儿子共度的感恩节在家中度过
Facebook petition urgent people now
现在Facebook的请愿书迫切人
the shop on Thanksgiving has more than 6000 likes its just wrong to make people work on a holiday meant for friends and family to be together
在感恩节的店铺已超过6000喜欢它只是错误地使人们的工作就意味着朋友和家人度假待在一起
the manager of the pizza hut in Elkhart Indiana said he was fired when you refuse a franchise owners order to open today spoke to MSNBC the Ed Schultz
在印第安纳州埃尔克哈特必胜客的经理说，当你拒绝一个特许经营业主为了今天开采访了MSNBC的埃德舒尔茨，他被解雇了
not right I don't agree with it and I'm not going to grade open a store
不对，我不同意这点，我不打算年级开设了专卖店
this morning Pizza Hut corporate headquarters stepped in any was offered his job back
今天上午必胜客公司总部临危受命，任何被提供了他的工作后面
Kmart in Chicago Joel Meyer had two carts of Games dolls and toys all to be given away to children's charities how good deal
凯玛特在芝加哥乔尔迈耶有游戏娃娃和玩具两辆大车都将赠送给儿童慈善机构如何处理好
I probably price
我大概价格
Christmas toys for kids
圣诞玩具的孩子
shopping on Thanksgiving is deluding Black Friday solo BB comparing these crowded the crowds tomorrow morning
在感恩节购物明早是自欺欺人黑色星期五独奏BB比较这些拥挤的人群
John yang thanks so much so what will the weather be like for all those bargain hunters tomorrow meteorologist Genesis hospital from the Weather Center
约翰·杨感谢这么多这么会出现什么天气像所有那些逢低买进​​明天气象学成因从气象中心医院
Janice is going to be quiet tomorrow just like it was today from coast to coast not much going on chili conditions in the East mild outWest tomorrow Friday for the shoppers will be sunny in Boston downtown Washington Atlanta temperatures in the 50s
卫兰会明天要安静，就像今天是从东海岸到西海岸没有太大的明天怎么回事辣椒条件在东轻度outWest周五购物者将以晴在波士顿市中心的华盛顿亚特兰大气温在50年代
Miami you be in the 70's clear in Chicago out towards Denver and San Francisco shoppers in the Pacific Northwest that's about it but it looks like for the big travel day coming up for Sunday the only place is going to see the major problems will probably be the Seattle area
迈阿密你是在70年代明确在芝加哥，向着丹佛和旧金山的购物者在西北太平洋地区仅此而已，但它看起来像大旅游日即将到来的周日的唯一地方是要看到存在的主要问题将可能是西雅图地区
heavy rain expected on Sunday and may be snow in the mountains the rest of the country would be nice and quiet
大雨预计在周日，可能是积雪的山国其他地区将是很好，安静
looking good Janice tanks tonight we are just 48 hours from a cell phone POS deadline by the White House to turn around the Obamacare website and get it working for most users at the same time is another race happening to get younger people to sign up for health insurance and order to make that
看起来不错关颖坦克今晚我们是从手机的POS期限只有48个小时的白宫扭转Obamacare的网站，并得到它的同时工作对于大多数用户来说是另一场比赛发生的事情让年轻人报名参加健康保险和为了使该
happens to kids are hoping parents will make the picture their grown children
碰巧的孩子都希望父母会让画面成年子女
Brad from the dinner table tonight at the store now for my White House correspondent Peter Alexander
布拉德从饭桌今晚在店里现在我的白宫记者彼得·亚历山大
Topshop Mario
Topshop的马里奥
27 year old Nathan she's just to ensure that Obamacare supporters are counting on sheets to work for the homeless center of the so-called young Invincibles in Roman is critical to make a new law work AOL sign up what's the holdup
27岁的内森，她只是以确保Obamacare的支持者都指望表来工作的所谓年轻的不败在罗马的无家可归者中心的关键是要建立一个新的法律工作AOL的注册有什么滞留
just haven't gotten around 2 a.m.
只是还没有围绕上午02时得到
so how do you get young people onboard recruit their parents with a dose of humor AR
所以你如何让年轻人板载招聘父母与幽默AR剂量
PBS org mothers and their children DC ecards get health insurance so I can stop pestering you to sign up and start pressure you to get married
PBS组织的母亲和她们的孩子直流电子贺卡获得医疗保险，所以我可以别再缠着你注册并开始压力你要结婚了
we have something really important to talk to you about this new attitudes moms and dads have the talk with their grown kids over the holidays we know you don't have health insurance
我们有一些非常重要的，你谈谈这个新的态度的爸爸妈妈们与他们的孩子长大了，我们知道你没有医疗保险的假期谈话
we love you no matter what it is time to get covered shut up store power to Olivia Wilde go to the carousel free
我们爱你，不管它是什么时间去覆盖闭嘴店权力奥利维亚·王尔德去自由旋转木马
to succeed Obamacare needs young healthy adult awesome because of poor people with pre-existing condition
成功Obamacare的需要，因为穷人与预先存在的条件下，年轻健康的成年人真棒
advocate say there are encouraging size in California the first state to report who's in rolling through October 18 to 3400 data for 22 percent of enrollment slightly higher than their share the population
倡导者说，有令人鼓舞的大小在加利福尼亚州的第一个状态报告谁在通过10月18日滚动到3400的数据招生比他们的份额略高于22％的人口
invincible and I like to say young and stupid BlueCross and ass on the actually know that there an actual weight from actually having a $50
无敌的，我想说的年轻和愚蠢的蓝十字和屁股上居然知道，有一个实际的重量与实际有50美元
beginning this January 7 Hardwick a nursing student work part time what health insurance for the first time in 6 years
这起1月7日哈德威克护理学生工作兼职什么医疗保险首次6年
suburban that has been lifted because you don't know what the future holds but you have to prepare for it
郊区已被解除，因为你不知道将来会怎样，但你必须为它做准备
still there are obstacles California state run website is working supporters were the Florida federal site storage more young people from signing up
还是有障碍加利福尼亚州运行的网站正在支持者在佛罗里达州联邦现场存储更多的年轻人从签约
Peter Alexander NBC News Los Angeles
彼得·亚历山大NBC新闻洛杉矶
steelhead tonight the American oil boom bringing gas
今晚虹鳟美国石油繁荣带来天然气
prices down below $3 a gallon in what country big deal for millions holiday track and later the hound who just made history of the biggest Asian parents
价格向下跌破每加仑3美元的国家有什么大不了数以百万计的度假轨道，后来谁刚做的最大的亚洲父母的历史猎犬
back now with falling gas prices across the country down 49 cents a gallon from their pic this year and when gas prices drop consumers more likely use extra money to buy gifts solving fueled by the American oil boom and we get our report a knife mendeecees Harris Smith
返现与下跌的天然气价格在全国范围内下跌49美分一加仑，从今年他们的图片，当天然气价格下降消费者更倾向于使用多余的钱买礼物求解带动下，美国的石油繁荣，我们得到我们的报告一把刀mendeecees哈里斯·史密斯
an American boomtown Chickasha Oklahoma
美国的新兴城市奇克谢俄克拉何马州
meet Herald hand Eric Roberson
满足先驱手埃里克·罗伯逊
what's a self-made billionaire Harold is bullish on American oil
什么是一个白手起家的亿万富翁哈罗德是看好美国的石油
how much oil is there in the United States Berber ports in the world sorry Rabea hang on a second
多少油有没有在世界美国柏柏尔端口对不起Rabea挂在第二
United States has more oil in Saudi Arabia yeah by far
美国目前有更多的石油在沙特阿拉伯耶
Harold Hamm is in Oklahoma who controls more oil underground anyone else in the US
哈罗德·哈姆是在俄克拉荷马谁控制更多的石油井下任何人在美国
thanks everyone get out and help Hafeez pool supply for 40 years and all this was here Headley I have the technology
感谢大家走出去，帮助哈菲兹池供电40年，这一切都在这里海德利我有技术
so it's a different from a different H&D this doctor at grandaddy's Rey
所以这是一个不同的从不同的H＆D这名医生在grandaddy的雷伊
oil rigs one by Joey sticks and software
石油钻井平台一个接乔伊棍棒和软件
fine tune to find black gold in natural gas places in possibly the week
微调找到黑金天然气的地方可能是一周
America's producing 50 percent more oil than just 5 years ago almost 8 million barrels today and that is a big deal
美国生产50％以上的石油比仅有5年前增加近800万桶今天，这是一个大问题
big deal for on eBay inforce die find work in California
大不了在eBay上有效保单死找工作在加州
starting job in the oil rigs pays more than $60
开始的工作在石油钻机支付60元以上
very good for a guy like me with no college education
很不错的像我这样的家伙，没有大专以上学历
prospect South Australia
展望南澳大利亚
big deal in oil patch town like Chickasha economic development director
大不了在油斑镇像奇克谢的经济发展总监
Christy Elkin says household income has jobs within 25 percent in the last 2 years
克里斯蒂说，埃尔金家庭收入中有25％的工作在过去的2年
shot in the arm but it's also been in a door opening 22 possibilities in Central Park community
射中手臂，但它也一直处于开门在中央公园社区22可能性
big deal for American consumers or seen gasoline prices decline
大不了美国消费者或看到汽油价格下滑
this is the sum will the Texas because of horizontal drilling
这是由于水平井钻井的总和将德州
summit 23 seismic activity Andrew in water
峰会23地震活动安德鲁在水中
mini environmental groups in a moratorium on fracking in all out band
在压裂暂停迷你环保团体在所有带外
what ham and others in the oil industry insist it safe
什么火腿和其他在石油行业坚持它的安全
ham says old is new oil production has another benefit it means a great deal
火腿老说是新的石油产量已经另一个好处则意味着大量的
NBA Benedum on the shelf
NBA奔杜姆在货架上
energy independence imagine
能源独立想象
Harry Smith NBC News Chickasha Oklahoma
哈里·史密斯NBC新闻奇克谢俄克拉何马州
back in a moment with a hopeful come back tonight after a big Olympics care
早在一个充满希望的时刻回来了今晚大奥运护理
is better run on the nation's food pantries in the week leading up to this Thanksgiving the man has sores after 5 billion dollars in cuts to the federal food stamp program at the start of November tonight a lot of families are finding them selves without even the basics to prepare a holiday meal
是对国家的食物餐具室在一周更好的运行领导到这个感恩的人已经疮后的5十亿美元削减到11月初今晚很多家庭的联邦食品券计划都发现他们的自我，甚至没有基本知识准备节日餐
are report part of the NBC new series on poverty we call in plain sight is supported by a grant from the Ford Foundation worn out from embassies Janet shamlian
被报告的贫困，我们在众目睽睽下称NBC的新系列的一部分，是支持福特基金会的资助从使馆珍妮特shamlian累死了
nations porn
国家色情
can barely keep the shell stop this food pantry outside and Corey Smith on every week fetus a problem
只能勉强保持外壳制止这种食品储藏室外面和科里·史密斯在每周胎儿有问题
heart breaker trying to do something
心脏断路器试图做一些事情
linear first timer switch pantry 47 million Americans hard hit by food stamps
线性第一定时开关储藏室47000000美国人重创粮票
director Mack Street Madison pantries providing record 6700 tanks giving me a
导演麦克街麦迪逊茶水间提供创纪录的6700坦克给我一个
pictures of cross a country or feeling at a level of demand and seen in years as a NuWave a client 60 to merge in seafood and Thanksgiving dinner
图片穿越一个国家或感觉在需求的水平，可见年的NuWave一个客户端60的海鲜和感恩节晚餐合并
times are heading home where in Murfreesboro Tennessee with 3 children get 36 dollars left eats month in food stamps
时代在回家的地方田纳西州莫非斯堡有3个孩子被甩在36美元吃一个月的粮票
dollars go salon ways actually we can probably be 3 days on that at least
美元去发廊的方式其实我们大概可以上3天以上
public assistance Ganek bakery close in Christmas Eve
在圣诞节前夕的公共援助Ganek面包店接近
St in
在圣
you don't really want to tell people what we do when we were hoping I would work out
你并不真的想告诉人们我们做什么，当我们希望自己能制定出
receiving food pantry just like Millions
接受食品储藏室就像数以百万计
is a responsibility to help the community do better person
是有责任帮助社会做更好的人
in the season of Plenty still an abundance of me
在丰盛的季节还是我丰盈
Jennifer AMLI on NBC News
珍妮弗在阿姆利NBC新闻
tonight scientist say the so-called comet of the century is probably a goner it doesn't appear to have survived journey around the Sun today there it is
今晚的科学家说，本世纪所谓的彗星可能是它不会出现到今天已存活围绕太阳的旅程有它是一个完了
in the lower part of your screen and now watch it goes away sin to say they saw the comet Ison approach the Sun but nothing came out on the other side that means the spectacular light show a lot of social hoping for
在屏幕的下方，现在看着它消失的罪说他们看到伊森彗星接近太阳，但没有出来的另一边，这意味着壮观的灯光表演了很多社会希望
is on likely to happen
是对可能发生
Lindsey Vonn said today she's back on the shelves for the first time since I bring a partial ACL tear in her right knee in practice last week for the pictures
林赛沃恩说，今天她重新上架的第一次，因为我带来了部分ACL撕裂她的右膝在实践中上周的照片
postage us today on Facebook yesterday on the Today Show Bond talk to Matt Lauer about her most recent injury normally Sheen stop competing to have it repaired but instead of helping to compete next week in order to get ready for the Olympics in Sochi in just about 11 weeks
邮资今天我们在Facebook昨日对今日秀邦德跟马特·劳尔关于她最近的损伤通常辛停止争相把它修好，但不是帮助下周竞争，以获得为奥运会做好准备在索契，在短短约11周
when we come back saloon very good dogs but only one can be named Best in Show
当我们回来的轿车很不错的狗，但只有一个可以被命名为最佳展示
are final story tonight about an annual tradition for a lot of families on Thanksgiving Day gathering around the TV to watch the National dog show
是最后的故事今晚约一年一度的传统为很多家庭在感恩节聚会围着电视观看全国狗展
more than $2000 computer for the title but only one can be named Best in Show and we get the story from embassies Miguel Almaguer
2000元以上电脑的称号，但只有一个可以被命名为最佳展示，我们从使馆米格尔Almaguer得到的故事
welcome back to the National dog show is it just a competition dizzy Israel
欢迎回到全国狗展是它只是一个竞争头晕以色列
this is a black tie event seriously this could be anybody show today with 20000 dollars and steak last year 20 million viewers couldn't get enough heavy bones
这是一个黑色领带事件严重的今天可能是任何人秀20000美元和牛排，去年2000万的观众无法得到足够重的骨头
intimidating
恐吓
who's who of Brie
谁是布里谁
Leshawna eats queen bees the sum of the street Usain who from the toy group Pekingese what some like inside
Leshawna吃蜂王街道乌塞恩的总和谁从玩具组北京人有的像里面有什么
telogen comical
休止期滑稽
the more than makeup for incontinence
比化妆失禁更
infact sometimes you can be hard to tell who's walking who
逸岸有时你可能很难分辨谁是谁走